<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<graphml xmlns="http://graphml.graphdrawing.org/xmlns" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://graphml.graphdrawing.org/xmlns http://graphml.graphdrawing.org/xmlns/1.0/graphml.xsd">
  <key id="d6" for="edge" attr.name="source_id" attr.type="string" />
  <key id="d5" for="edge" attr.name="keywords" attr.type="string" />
  <key id="d4" for="edge" attr.name="description" attr.type="string" />
  <key id="d3" for="edge" attr.name="weight" attr.type="double" />
  <key id="d2" for="node" attr.name="source_id" attr.type="string" />
  <key id="d1" for="node" attr.name="description" attr.type="string" />
  <key id="d0" for="node" attr.name="entity_type" attr.type="string" />
  <graph edgedefault="undirected">
    <node id="&quot;HEATHER JACK&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Heather Jack is a family member who prepared a meal for an elderly woman and her son with muscular dystrophy last Christmas Eve."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5bc48f86f7cbdd4c755d0199e250ab88</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;NEIGHBORHOOD&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The location where Heather and her family prepared a meal for the elderly woman and her son is not specified in the text."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5bc48f86f7cbdd4c755d0199e250ab88</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;GARY AND DEBRA DANOFF&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Gary and Debra Danoff are two individuals involved in an act of volunteerism, preparing meals for homeless shelters."&lt;SEP&gt;"Gary and Debra Danoff is a family that spent Christmas morning at the Washington, D. C. Jewish Community Center (JCC).")</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5bc48f86f7cbdd4c755d0199e250ab88&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-adab8dfdce6295ef7521ee302a7cf6db</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;VOLUNTEER FAMILY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Volunteer Family is an organization based in Boston dedicated to matching families with volunteer opportunities, both during the holidays and year-round."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-adab8dfdce6295ef7521ee302a7cf6db</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;WASHINGTON, D. C. JEWISH COMMUNITY CENTER (JCC)&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The JCC is the location where the Danoffs spent Christmas morning preparing a feast for homeless shelters."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-adab8dfdce6295ef7521ee302a7cf6db</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;TOBY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Toby is the writer who is interested in having a specific type of racer."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-adab8dfdce6295ef7521ee302a7cf6db</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;AUSTRALIANS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The Australians represent a group that implemented a policy to prevent drinking and driving, indicating a public health initiative."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-d9b94bc1838752c9758ae25df703ff72</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;DRIVER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Drivers are the primary users of the invention, indicating its relevance to daily life."&lt;SEP&gt;"The driver is part of Peter's family who has a lot of servants."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-1d6fd0cb36274a8dfd4f4bf9154cd2c8&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-d9b94bc1838752c9758ae25df703ff72</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SCIENTIST&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The scientist is the inventor of the device that connects the TV to an exercise bike, showing a creative approach to solving a problem."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-d9b94bc1838752c9758ae25df703ff72</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;FOOTBALL SHOES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"DEVICE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The shoes are the object of interest, showing their function as footwear."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-d9b94bc1838752c9758ae25df703ff72</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;BUCKINGHAM PALACE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Buckingham Palace is a historical location with a long history and has been in use for various purposes over the centuries."&lt;SEP&gt;"Buckingham Palace is a location where events such as the Queen's Gallery opening are held, indicating its significance in the daily schedule."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-f62f2de5415bdb2128c7b4bbd6118c2c&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-2c07e9270723bc4d525ba7001b4f292a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;THE QUEEN'S GALLERY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The Queen's Gallery is a location where events like the opening of the Palace State rooms are held, indicating its importance in the daily schedule."&lt;SEP&gt;"The Queen's Gallery is a location within Buckingham Palace where fine paintings and works of art are displayed."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-f62f2de5415bdb2128c7b4bbd6118c2c&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-0e7268d3bed1e88cb6e33d645fa3a629</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ST. JAMES'S PARK&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"St. James's Park is a location mentioned in the context of a potential visit to all the listed locations, suggesting it is one of the options for a visit on July 3 at 3 o'clock."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-f62f2de5415bdb2128c7b4bbd6118c2c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;TU YOUYOU&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Tu Youyou is a native Chinese who was educated and works in China to win the Lasker award, making her the first native Chinese to receive the award."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-e7adf230541b74b6b95df8f43237cfe4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CHINA&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"China is a country with its own distinct traffic rules, where traffic moves on the right side of the road.")&lt;SEP&gt;"China is mentioned as a location where the increase in obesity is occurring, indicating a geographical context."&lt;SEP&gt;"China is mentioned as one of the countries involved in the International Summit on Human Gene Editing."&lt;SEP&gt;"China is mentioned as setting up more than 2,400 nature reserves, covering over 15 percent of its land area."&lt;SEP&gt;"China is the country Beijing is a part of, showing a country-level connection."&lt;SEP&gt;"China is the country hosting the China International Fair for Investment and Trade in Xiamen."&lt;SEP&gt;"China is the location where Shenzhou-9 spacecraft was launched and where the crew will complete the first manned space docking mission."&lt;SEP&gt;"China is the location where the baiji, a fresh water dolphin, is native to and was declared extinct due to water pollution."&lt;SEP&gt;"China is the location where the currency devaluation occurs, affecting global trade and economic relations."&lt;SEP&gt;"China is the location where the school bus safety rules came into force."&lt;SEP&gt;"China is the location where the special day for singles is celebrated."&lt;SEP&gt;"China is the only country in the world that has set up a special day for singles to celebrate their lives."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-e7adf230541b74b6b95df8f43237cfe4&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-4c8f775ba2c56f3ed08672f63eaa49c2&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-dc8eea62532cd43fed266f6e574d0782&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-93901f246d60b9f0eabd95102ac4e998&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-ea48f5352c061a0d9fd36906f69b81c2&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-611fb27ef3c15c1adaf70de79e3055a5&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-867f4ce3c98e86e94fe987e40c122929&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-b5ecb746018edf4c971c3f42154dfb06&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-7d9d93230fc219580c6011b84bcf0ccb&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-a23a47217d8f71ac1ac9a737cb0f25ed&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-b23ca935d067b6258ef4f7082bc32af1</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ENVIRONMENT&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Environment refers to the surroundings of a living thing, including the atmosphere, land, and water."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-e7adf230541b74b6b95df8f43237cfe4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PROTECT&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ACTION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Protecting the environment is an action aimed at preserving and maintaining ecological balance."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-e7adf230541b74b6b95df8f43237cfe4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;EDUCATE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ACTION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Educating the public on environmental issues is an action to increase awareness and promote sustainable practices."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-e7adf230541b74b6b95df8f43237cfe4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;THREATS TO EARTH&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"TOPIC"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Threats to Earth refer to the various dangers and issues facing the planet."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-e7adf230541b74b6b95df8f43237cfe4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;GLOBAL WARMING&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"TOPIC"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Global Warming is a significant environmental issue characterized by the increase in Earth's average temperature."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-e7adf230541b74b6b95df8f43237cfe4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;POLLUTION&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"TOPIC"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Pollution refers to the contamination of air, water, and land by harmful substances."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-e7adf230541b74b6b95df8f43237cfe4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;RENEWABLE ENERGY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"TOPIC"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Renewable Energy sources are methods that produce power without depleting natural resources."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-e7adf230541b74b6b95df8f43237cfe4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;FRESHWATER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"TOPIC"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Freshwater is essential for life and is a topic of concern regarding its availability and conservation."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-e7adf230541b74b6b95df8f43237cfe4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;INTERNATIONAL FAIR FOR INVESTMENT AND TRADE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"EVENT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The event referred to is the International Fair for Investment and Trade, which is drawing global attention."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-06dcd7b5f53c2fa897347f32e691670b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ZHUYAYAN&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"ZhuYayan is the mayor of a location where the International Fair for Investment and Trade is taking place."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-06dcd7b5f53c2fa897347f32e691670b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SYDNEY UNIVERSITY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Sydney University is the institution where the robotic research took place."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-06dcd7b5f53c2fa897347f32e691670b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;DR. KENDRA KERRISK&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Dr. Kendra Kerrisk is a dairy researcher associated with the Sydney University's Centre for Field Robotics."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-06dcd7b5f53c2fa897347f32e691670b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;FARMERS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Farmers are mentioned as one of the factors contributing to the increase in the black bear population."&lt;SEP&gt;"Farmers are the end-users of the robotic technology in this context."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-06dcd7b5f53c2fa897347f32e691670b&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-b16865faaeac180b9464a1919f9e4e22</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;COWS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ANIMAL"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Cows are the subject of the robotic technology being tested."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-06dcd7b5f53c2fa897347f32e691670b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ROBOTS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"TECHNOLOGY"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Robots are the automated machines used for various tasks, including moving cows in this case."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-06dcd7b5f53c2fa897347f32e691670b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;HUMAN&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Humans operate the robots and are involved in the dairy farming process."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-06dcd7b5f53c2fa897347f32e691670b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ART WORKS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ARTIFACT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Art works, such as paintings of Fitzgerald's son, are part of the collection being auctioned."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-06dcd7b5f53c2fa897347f32e691670b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SUN YANG&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Sun Yang is a swimmer who set a new world record for China and won two Olympic gold medals in swimming at the 2012 London Olympic Games.")</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-9a9501212f2948ef887f9eb630a89634</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;AUTHOR&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The author is a person who wrote the text, likely a journalist or author of the text."&lt;SEP&gt;"The author of the text is not explicitly identified, but it is implied to be the author of Pliny's letter to a friend, as the text is a direct quote from a letter."&lt;SEP&gt;"The author of the text is the person who wrote the passage."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-26f1a855dd5794e4d0cbbb263ff5c8f2&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-319a207bec74e8aeb9c7f5141164de5f&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-e743116b36068d79b93850a992cf153c</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;2012 LONDON OLYMPIC GAMES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"EVENT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The 2012 London Olympic Games is an event that took place in 2012."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-26f1a855dd5794e4d0cbbb263ff5c8f2</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;UNITED STATES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The United States is a country known for its cultural traditions and holidays."&lt;SEP&gt;"The United States is a country, indicating a political and geographical entity."&lt;SEP&gt;"The United States is a country."&lt;SEP&gt;"The United States is an organization that is not part of the Kyoto Protocol."&lt;SEP&gt;"The United States is the country where Owens was not honored until 1976."&lt;SEP&gt;"The tax is imposed on alpha mined in the United States, indicating a specific geographical context."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-c36c64494dfabc5fd311ebc67bc93081&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-8d57836cacff8833aa3ff524429b7ad6&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-a4eb0cffd10d7afe0dae1bb8a90b3848&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-c4adcc4d5934f45ddaab615c25987990&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-26f1a855dd5794e4d0cbbb263ff5c8f2&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-e51a355daae6b88997131de8dd11919a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CHRISTINE WILLIAMS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Christine Williams is the main character in the passage, who participated in the national Division II cross-country championships after her sister's death."&lt;SEP&gt;"Christine Williams is the middle of three sisters, indicating her family background and age difference with her sisters."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-9651f4c9a49c8dc02bcfbd9abb31ccb8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;KERRY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Kerry is one of Christine Williams' sisters, who is 25 years old."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-9651f4c9a49c8dc02bcfbd9abb31ccb8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;JENNIFER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Jennifer is another sister of Christine Williams, who is 18 years old."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-9651f4c9a49c8dc02bcfbd9abb31ccb8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;WILLIAMS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Williams is the middle of three sisters, indicating her family background and age difference with her sisters."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-9651f4c9a49c8dc02bcfbd9abb31ccb8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;METROPOLITAN GOVERNMENT OF MEMPHIS AND SHELBY COUNTY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The Metropolitan Government of Memphis and Shelby County is the governing body of Memphis, Tennessee, responsible for city-level operations and services."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-172d4583f8dea3fd949d0b25279c45b9</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SIX HUNDRED FIFTY THOUSAND PEOPLE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The Metropolitan Government of Memphis and Shelby County is home to six hundred fifty thousand people, indicating its population size."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-172d4583f8dea3fd949d0b25279c45b9</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MORE THAN ONE MILLION PEOPLE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The Metropolitan Government of Memphis and Shelby County is also home to more than one million people, indicating its population size."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-172d4583f8dea3fd949d0b25279c45b9</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;AFRICAN AMERICAN&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"About forty eight percent of the city's population is African American, indicating the racial composition of the population."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-172d4583f8dea3fd949d0b25279c45b9</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MEMPHIS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Memphis is the location where the events described in the text took place, including the civil rights movement and the murder of Martin Luther King Jr."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-bd7d71bfed69f8c341743781322e9c3a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MARTIN LUTHER KING JR.&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Martin Luther King Jr. is the famous civil rights leader who was assassinated in Memphis."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-bd7d71bfed69f8c341743781322e9c3a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;W*E HERENTON&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"W*E Herenton is the first black mayor of Memphis."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-bd7d71bfed69f8c341743781322e9c3a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;AFRICAN AMERICANS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"African Americans refers to people of African descent living in Memphis."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-bd7d71bfed69f8c341743781322e9c3a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;NATIONAL CIVIL RIGHTS MUSEUM&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The National Civil Rights Museum is an organization located in Memphis, which is significant for its role in the American civil rights movement."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-bd7d71bfed69f8c341743781322e9c3a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;TOWN MANAGER LESLIE STANLEY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Town Manager Leslie Stanley is the person responsible for addressing the dam problem in Hampden, Maine."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-4dbbc2a1e13ea51f5539c081de225966</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;JACK&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Jack is the boy narrating the story, who takes care of his ill mother and has a close relationship with his neighbors."&lt;SEP&gt;"Jack is the individual who invited the beggar to dinner and later becomes involved in the conflict with the beavers."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-4dbbc2a1e13ea51f5539c081de225966&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-e19ac0ea9ce7df7b442c840ae7a6b627</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;WOMAN&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The woman is the beggar who invites Jack to dinner and later helps him start his own business."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-4dbbc2a1e13ea51f5539c081de225966</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;OLD JACK&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Old Jack is a character mentioned in the text who is associated with the beggar and the business start."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-4dbbc2a1e13ea51f5539c081de225966</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;BEAVERS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The beavers are the group responsible for building the dam, which causes the problem for the town."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-4dbbc2a1e13ea51f5539c081de225966</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;YOUNG BEAVERS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The young beavers are a new group of beavers that continues the dam-building activity."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-4dbbc2a1e13ea51f5539c081de225966</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;WORLD FOOD PROGRAM&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"WFP is an organization focused on preventing hunger and providing food assistance worldwide."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-73ae387df2a6e35e21aee7fcf5ddb76a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;OLDER BEAVERS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The strategy used by authorities in Hampden, Maine, seems to be based on working with older beavers, suggesting a method of dealing with dam troubles."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-73ae387df2a6e35e21aee7fcf5ddb76a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;YOUNGER BEAVERS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Similarly, the strategy seems to involve working with younger beavers, implying a different approach to managing the dam problem."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-73ae387df2a6e35e21aee7fcf5ddb76a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;DAM TROUBLE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Dam trouble refers to the issues faced by authorities in Hampden, Maine, concerning the dam built by beavers."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-73ae387df2a6e35e21aee7fcf5ddb76a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;HAMPDEN, MAINE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Hampden, Maine is a location where the dam trouble occurred.")</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-73ae387df2a6e35e21aee7fcf5ddb76a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;GRANDMA MOSES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Grandma Moses is a renowned painter who became famous partially due to her age and simple approach to art."&lt;SEP&gt;"Grandma Moses is an artist known for her simple and cheerful paintings of American farm life, becoming famous in her seventies."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-2e9de0040e3a0dbb78f32159f716709e&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-0b9a9c192485b2833c95724a8a39e749</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;WILLOW TREE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANISM"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The willow tree that attacked caterpillars changed the chemistry of its leaves."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-2e9de0040e3a0dbb78f32159f716709e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MS WATSON&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Ms Watson is the main subject of the text, traveling through various oceans and facing challenges such as storms and accidents."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-23334d33e946c642ab261d69e1851fa5</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;TOM&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Tom is the father of Rachel and Melissa."&lt;SEP&gt;"Tom is the main character described in the text."&lt;SEP&gt;"Tom is the main character in the story, who experiences a traumatic event and makes a difficult decision to live."&lt;SEP&gt;"Tom is the main subject of the passage, described for his fun-loving nature, musical abilities, and popularity among friends."&lt;SEP&gt;"Tom is the person who goes to work by train and buys a newspaper every morning."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-93185d9d3b135cc03faafcbedac4a8ad&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-5e106c3607ab331e17494bc97f475886&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-5b555aba0363adca7fdcb5beb10a70de&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-23334d33e946c642ab261d69e1851fa5&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-413dc6dedd16a5002817273199f80619</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;AUSTRALIA&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Australia is the place where Tom lives."&lt;SEP&gt;"Australia is the subject of the passage, described as a country with valuable natural resources and a rich history."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-ad5a7554ace97afe7049fb53efa077d1&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-23334d33e946c642ab261d69e1851fa5</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;EUROPE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Europe is the location of the Airbus A380 assembly line."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-23334d33e946c642ab261d69e1851fa5</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;AIRBUS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Airbus is mentioned as hoping to sell 750 new planes, indicating its business activities and market presence."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0241310d0bd15259d44adb6979d61963</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;A380&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"AIRCRAFT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"A380 is mentioned as having 129 firm orders and 52 options, indicating its production and sales status."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0241310d0bd15259d44adb6979d61963</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SCHOOL SHOOTING&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"EVENT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The recent school shooting in Finland is mentioned as a significant event that has caused a need for stricter gun laws."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0241310d0bd15259d44adb6979d61963</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PATE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Pate is the defendant in the lawsuit, involved in a psychiatric malpractice case."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-d08874860c30de3a8a492d7498b9c60d</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;GARY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Gary is a character in the story who provides guidance and advice to Erica about the value of taking a relaxed approach to the camp trip."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-18bcf4955699f1967847280e540eba94</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ERICA&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Erica is the main character in the story who expresses her disinterest in the camp trip and her desire to see some amazing things and make great friends."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-18bcf4955699f1967847280e540eba94</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;JOHN&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"John is one of the people living in the houses mentioned by Corky."&lt;SEP&gt;"John is the little boy who goes home to tell Erica about the impending tree cutting."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-18bcf4955699f1967847280e540eba94&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-3ee3a64e9048bb17e5224abaa8512514</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;DOUGLAS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Douglas is a first-grade student who draws an empty hand as his thankful gesture, indicating his gratitude for his teacher's support and care."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-af4a2b637a35ca207c1eebe0e65176c3</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;BRITISH&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"British people are known for having a 'dry sense of humor' and not showing emotion, which is reflected in their jokes and the humor they use."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-af4a2b637a35ca207c1eebe0e65176c3</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;JULIAN TAN&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Julian Tan is a writer who has commented on British humor, highlighting the dryness of their sense of humor."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-af4a2b637a35ca207c1eebe0e65176c3</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;RICKY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Ricky is an English comedian known for his dry sense of humor."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-af4a2b637a35ca207c1eebe0e65176c3</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;HUFFPOST STUDENTS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"HuffPost Students is an online magazine that publishes content related to student life, humor, and culture."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-32c42cae37d4e6123df62a03e3ddf6a8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;RICKY GERVAIS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Ricky Gervais is an English comedian known for his dry sense of humor and his portrayal of sarcasm in his comedy routines."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-32c42cae37d4e6123df62a03e3ddf6a8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CHINA NATIONAL OPERA&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"China National Opera is a renowned opera company in China known for its productions and performances."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-32c42cae37d4e6123df62a03e3ddf6a8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;LI GUANGXI&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Li Guangxi is a vocalist associated with the China National Opera, known for her performances."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-32c42cae37d4e6123df62a03e3ddf6a8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;YAO HONG&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Yao Hong is another vocalist associated with the China National Opera."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-32c42cae37d4e6123df62a03e3ddf6a8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MADAME BUTTERFLY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Madame Butterfly is a Western opera classic featuring a character named 'Carmen Jones'."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-32c42cae37d4e6123df62a03e3ddf6a8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;LA TRAVIATA&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"La Traviata is a Western opera classic featuring a character named 'Violetta'."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-32c42cae37d4e6123df62a03e3ddf6a8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;RIGOLETTO&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Rigoletto is a Western opera classic featuring a character named 'Prokofiev'."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-32c42cae37d4e6123df62a03e3ddf6a8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CONCERT HALL&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"A concert hall is a venue for musical performances, such as concerts and operas."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-32c42cae37d4e6123df62a03e3ddf6a8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;NATIONAL LIBRARY OF CHINA&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The National Library of China is a cultural institution in China where events like concerts may take place."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-32c42cae37d4e6123df62a03e3ddf6a8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;FOLK ORCHESTRA OF THE CHINA OPERA AND BALLET THEATRE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The Folk Orchestra of the China Opera and Ballet Theatre is an orchestra associated with the China National Opera."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-32c42cae37d4e6123df62a03e3ddf6a8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MEMORY OF CHILDHOOD&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Memory of Childhood is a piece of traditional Chinese music."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-32c42cae37d4e6123df62a03e3ddf6a8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MEMORIAL CEREMONY FOR GOD&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Memorial Ceremony for God is a piece of traditional Chinese music."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-32c42cae37d4e6123df62a03e3ddf6a8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;WINE SONG&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Wine Song is a piece of traditional Chinese music."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-32c42cae37d4e6123df62a03e3ddf6a8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;I&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The girl who joined the cross-country team."), ("entity"</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-684d30ad080579c89469abe539defb8e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;TELEVISION&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"television is an organization that has influenced many aspects of society, including education, entertainment, and global communication.")</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-31df3cda225a6b08e7bb00a56a284935</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;HARRY POTTER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Harry Potter is a character in the Harry Potter series, a popular young wizard with a significant following."&lt;SEP&gt;"Harry Potter is a fictional concept of magical adventures and a popular culture phenomenon."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5fe9b8b4f81b68354055b1b64b32f36b&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-f9ff3ea174012d94f8bcaf2c8a851a47</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MACHINES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"TECHNOLOGY"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Machines are described as tools that can help with tasks, indicating their importance and necessity in modern life."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-f9ff3ea174012d94f8bcaf2c8a851a47</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;HOGWARTS CASTLE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Hogwarts Castle is the fictional home of the protagonist Harry Potter."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-f9ff3ea174012d94f8bcaf2c8a851a47</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;BRITISH HOTEL&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The Georgian Hotel in Central London is an organization that offers accommodation for Harry Potter fans."&lt;SEP&gt;"The Georgian Hotel in Central London is the location where the wizard chambers are located, making it suitable for Harry Potter fans."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5fe9b8b4f81b68354055b1b64b32f36b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SALLY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Sally is a character in the text who spends her school holiday with her mother at the Georgian Hotel."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5fe9b8b4f81b68354055b1b64b32f36b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PETER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Peter is a character in the text who experiences a fire with his family at his home."&lt;SEP&gt;"Peter is a little boy moving to a new city, living with his parents who are very rich."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5fe9b8b4f81b68354055b1b64b32f36b&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-1d6fd0cb36274a8dfd4f4bf9154cd2c8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;FIREMEN&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Firemen are the individuals who respond to emergencies like the fire at Peter's home."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5fe9b8b4f81b68354055b1b64b32f36b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MICHAEL JOSEPH JACKSON&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Michael Jackson is a well-known entertainer, musician, and philanthropist, born on August 29, 1958, in Gary, Indiana."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-7a01f50a350d17fe49dae5e83403dece</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;BEAUTY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Beauty is a concept that is often regarded as something praiseworthy.")</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-7a01f50a350d17fe49dae5e83403dece</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;TOMB SWEEPERS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"People who clean and tidy the graves on Tomb-sweeping Day."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-3668558218f0fe8b6186ab3e608a7f5e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;AMERICAN SOLDIER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Lee Duncan was an American soldier who performed acts of heroism during World War I."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-ef95e50a1deb4c430ee6a03df0ffbbe4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;HALF-STARVED SHEPHERD&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ANIMAL"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The shepherd and her puppies were half-starved animals rescued by Lee Duncan."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-ef95e50a1deb4c430ee6a03df0ffbbe4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;BOMBED DOG'S KENNEL&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The location where the dogs were found was a bombed dog's kennel."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-ef95e50a1deb4c430ee6a03df0ffbbe4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;LEE DUNCAN&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Lee Duncan is the individual who rescued the dogs."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-ef95e50a1deb4c430ee6a03df0ffbbe4</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;DUNCAN&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Duncan is the individual who made special arrangements to take his pups back to Los Angeles after the war."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-046d8a3ca38544ebc596fc09f443e54e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;NANNETTE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Nannette is the individual who became ill and died during the Atlantic crossing with Duncan's pups."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-046d8a3ca38544ebc596fc09f443e54e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;RIN TIN TIN&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Rin Tin Tin is the dog that performed at the LA dog show and later became involved in films and television series."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-046d8a3ca38544ebc596fc09f443e54e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;WARNERS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Warners is the film studio that hired Rin Tin Tin for the film 'Man From Hells River' and sponsored his radio show."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-046d8a3ca38544ebc596fc09f443e54e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ATLANTIC CROSSING&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"EVENT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The event that Duncan and Rin Tin Tin underwent during which Nannette became ill and died."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-046d8a3ca38544ebc596fc09f443e54e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MRS. MATTHEWS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Mrs. Matthews is a woman over sixty who has a special card that allows her to take buses without paying."&lt;SEP&gt;"Mrs. Matthews is a woman who lives in the country and uses a senior citizen's card to travel cheaply on the bus."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-a2198fb76fcd5ec86a98d8d1c60a4ef7&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-68a253586aafdfdcaf1daee891a49ed5</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SENIOR CITIZEN'S CARD&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"A card that allows senior citizens to travel cheaply on the bus."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-68a253586aafdfdcaf1daee891a49ed5</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MR. READ&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Mr. Read has a large farm near a hill and is busy with his day-to-day work."&lt;SEP&gt;"Mr. Read is the owner of the large farm near a hill."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-a2198fb76fcd5ec86a98d8d1c60a4ef7&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-68a253586aafdfdcaf1daee891a49ed5</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SONS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The sons are the children of Mr. Read, who are involved in helping their mother with the baby pigs."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-a2198fb76fcd5ec86a98d8d1c60a4ef7</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SCHOOLBAG&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ARTIFACT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The schoolbag is an artifact that the son threw on the table, indicating his readiness to help his mother."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-a2198fb76fcd5ec86a98d8d1c60a4ef7</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CANADA&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Canada is mentioned as the origin of the Environmental Children's Organization, indicating its nationality."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-11bbd666ecd8616c47cce779349f3c96</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;E.C.O.&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"E.C.O. is the name of the organization represented by the speaker, indicating its type."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-11bbd666ecd8616c47cce779349f3c96</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;BRITAIN&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Britain is mentioned as a place where the weather seems to change daily, indicating a significant role in the discussion about weather patterns."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-9c1a1db0f9a928810faa894a4ed75c94</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PEOPLE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"People are described as being affected by the weather, showing that weather patterns have a societal impact."&lt;SEP&gt;"People are described as volunteers for various Olympic Games, indicating a collective effort."&lt;SEP&gt;"The text does not mention a specific group of people by that name."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-319a207bec74e8aeb9c7f5141164de5f&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-b16865faaeac180b9464a1919f9e4e22&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-9c1a1db0f9a928810faa894a4ed75c94</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;TEXT&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ACTIVITY"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Text is a collection of information that can be analyzed and processed, often in a location such as a computer or a physical workspace."&lt;SEP&gt;"The text is a description of a walk, indicating that the setting is relevant to the discussion about walking and weather."&lt;SEP&gt;"The text is attributed to an author, suggesting that the author is an expert or writer on the topic of walking and exercise."&lt;SEP&gt;"Walking is described with specific tips for handling different weather conditions, suggesting that it is a relevant activity to the discussion about weather and exercise."&lt;SEP&gt;"Walking is described with specific tips for staying comfortable while walking, suggesting that it is a relevant activity to the discussion about exercise and comfort."&lt;SEP&gt;"Walking is mentioned as an exercise of choice for most dieters, indicating that it is a relevant activity to the discussion about dieting and exercise."&lt;SEP&gt;"Walking is mentioned as one of the safest activities, indicating that it is a relevant activity to the discussion about safety and exercise."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-7ed85e484e3aecbb6856ed6e7189d70e&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-9c1a1db0f9a928810faa894a4ed75c94</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MR. BELL&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Mr. Bell is one of the individuals involved in the bank robbery, assisting George with the money count."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-21ba3202af9441dd341397faf55a518b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MR. BURROWS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Mr. Burrows is the bank president and appears cheerful when meeting George."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-21ba3202af9441dd341397faf55a518b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;GEORGE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"George is the chief accountant who is robbed by Mr. Burrows and his associates."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-21ba3202af9441dd341397faf55a518b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SERVANTS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Servants are part of Peter's family who assist the wealthy parents."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-1d6fd0cb36274a8dfd4f4bf9154cd2c8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;DEBORAH DUFFEY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Deborah Duffey is the main character, a high school basketball player who dreams of becoming an outstanding player and playing college ball."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-4173ded2a25f24c57b03f25ea7d02247</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MILLS HIGH SCHOOL&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Mills High School is the location of the basketball game where Deborah's season ends in a knee injury."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-4173ded2a25f24c57b03f25ea7d02247</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;DEBORAH'S KNEE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"INJURY"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Deborah's knee injury is the central event that ends her high school basketball career."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-4173ded2a25f24c57b03f25ea7d02247</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;INJURY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"TYPE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The knee injury is of a debilitating nature, leading to a career change."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-4173ded2a25f24c57b03f25ea7d02247</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PHYSICAL THERAPIST&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"OCCUPATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Deborah's injury leads her to a career in Physical Therapy.")</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-4173ded2a25f24c57b03f25ea7d02247</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;FLEET FEET SPORTS TULSA&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Fleet Feet Sports Tulsa is a location where the race packet can be picked up during registration."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0ded6b34c68c9da39bc1008a6ee9fba3</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;DANIEL KALLIONTZIS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Daniel Kalliontzis is an IT consultant who came up with the idea for the smart sticker system."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-78a6c8aa0016d002ce51541a6b45acff</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;FRANKFURT-BASED&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Frankfurt is the location where Daniel Kalliontzis is based as an IT consultant."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-78a6c8aa0016d002ce51541a6b45acff</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;RANDY GRIM&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Randy Grim is the founder of Stray Rescue and a former stray dog owner."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-78a6c8aa0016d002ce51541a6b45acff</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ST. LOUIS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"St. Louis is the location where Stray Rescue operates and where the number of stray dogs has increased."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-78a6c8aa0016d002ce51541a6b45acff</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;EDWARD BURTON&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Edward Burton is the subject of the story, known for his bridge-playing and his ability to influence the author with his stories and humor."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-51bee59e08c7882f608fb9e14a80dbc1</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;FRIDA KAHLO&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Frida Kahlo is a renowned Mexican artist known for her influence on the art world and her personal struggles with polio and back injuries."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-51bee59e08c7882f608fb9e14a80dbc1</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;DIANNA&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Dianna Spencer is a person who was born into a wealthy family and later married to Prince Charles, giving birth to Prince William, Prince Harry, and has an interest in international charities."&lt;SEP&gt;"Dianna was married to Prince Charles and had a daughter with him named Prince William and Prince Harry."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-6922b755c459e10511a12c0ffac86e9f&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-2e3dea5c375f816845194c449142ef02</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;GWENT POLICE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Gwent Police is an organization responsible for policing in Gwent, UK."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-6922b755c459e10511a12c0ffac86e9f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;YSTRAD MYNACH STATION&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Ystrad Mynach station is a location within the UK."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-6922b755c459e10511a12c0ffac86e9f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;31 CELLS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"31 cells refer to a specific location within a facility."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-6922b755c459e10511a12c0ffac86e9f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PS5 MILLION&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"AMOUNT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"ps5 million refers to an amount of money."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-6922b755c459e10511a12c0ffac86e9f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;12 WITH A &quot;LIVE SCAN&quot; SYSTEM&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"12 cells with a 'live scan' system refer to a specific location within a facility."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-6922b755c459e10511a12c0ffac86e9f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;DRUNKEN OR DISTURBED PRISONERS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"GROUP"</data>
      <data key="d1">"drunken or disturbed prisoners refer to a group of individuals."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-6922b755c459e10511a12c0ffac86e9f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ALERTING OFFICERS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"DEVICE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"an alarm alertsing officers is a device used in the facility."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-6922b755c459e10511a12c0ffac86e9f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;COMMUNICATION&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ACTIVITY"</data>
      <data key="d1">"blue on the wall suggests a communication activity within the facility."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-6922b755c459e10511a12c0ffac86e9f</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MARY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Mary is a student at Xihu Middle School, enjoys red clothes, and has Chinese and English friends."&lt;SEP&gt;"Mary is an American girl who is now in Beijing with her parents. She is studying Chinese and is learning to speak it well."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-e9babfa78d4c27189bf6053e2b0c8a60&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-2e3dea5c375f816845194c449142ef02</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PRINCE CHARLES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Prince Charles is the husband of Dianna."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-2e3dea5c375f816845194c449142ef02</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PRINCE WILLIAM&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Prince William is one of the children born to Dianna and Prince Charles."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-2e3dea5c375f816845194c449142ef02</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PRINCE HARRY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Prince Harry is another child born to Dianna and Prince Charles."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-2e3dea5c375f816845194c449142ef02</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;1961&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"DATE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"1961 is the year when Dianna married Prince Charles."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-2e3dea5c375f816845194c449142ef02</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;1981&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"DATE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"1981 is the year when Dianna got married to Prince Charles again."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-2e3dea5c375f816845194c449142ef02</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;1991&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"DATE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"1991 is the year when Dianna visited the hospital to see AIDS patients with Barbara Bush."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-2e3dea5c375f816845194c449142ef02</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;1997&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"DATE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"1997 is the year when Dianna died."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-2e3dea5c375f816845194c449142ef02</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;BRITISH PRIME MINISTER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Tony Blair was the British Prime Minister at the time of Dianna's death."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-2e3dea5c375f816845194c449142ef02</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PRINCE DIANA&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Prince Diana was the People's Princess and was known for her philanthropy and social work."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-2e3dea5c375f816845194c449142ef02</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;18&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"AGE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Dianna was 18 years old when she got married to Prince Charles."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-2e3dea5c375f816845194c449142ef02</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;20&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"AGE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Dianna was 20 years old when she got married to Prince Charles for the second time."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-2e3dea5c375f816845194c449142ef02</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;22&quot;(&quot;ENTITY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"MARY"</data>
      <data key="d1">"person"</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-2e3dea5c375f816845194c449142ef02</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;GLA ELECTRONICS OF AMERICA INC.&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"GLA Electronics is an organization that manufactures and sells cell phones."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0f65bdd311ee18f5a908e4723e90e112</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CARPHONE QUARTERLY SALES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"CarPhone Quarterly Sales is an organization responsible for tracking and reporting on car phone sales."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0f65bdd311ee18f5a908e4723e90e112</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;BRIAN FISHER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Brian Fisher is the CEO of GLA Electronics of America Inc."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0f65bdd311ee18f5a908e4723e90e112</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;VENICE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Venice is a city known for its canals and historical significance."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0f65bdd311ee18f5a908e4723e90e112</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ANT&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANISM"</data>
      <data key="d1">"An ant is an organism that lives in colonies and moves on land."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0f65bdd311ee18f5a908e4723e90e112</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;BEE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANISM"</data>
      <data key="d1">"A bee is an insect that collects nectar and pollen."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0f65bdd311ee18f5a908e4723e90e112</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;BUTTERFLY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANISM"</data>
      <data key="d1">"A butterfly is a flying insect that undergoes metamorphosis."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0f65bdd311ee18f5a908e4723e90e112</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;GIRAFFE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANISM"</data>
      <data key="d1">"A giraffe is a large herbivorous mammal known for its long neck."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0f65bdd311ee18f5a908e4723e90e112</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;AAAS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The AAAS is an organization that displays enthusiasm for liberal education and is tasked with clarifying a report on education reform."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0b9a9c192485b2833c95724a8a39e749</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MOON CAKE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"EVENT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The story revolves around the Moon Cake, a traditional Chinese festival cake that has historical significance."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0b9a9c192485b2833c95724a8a39e749</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;YUAN DYNASTY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The Yuan dynasty was a historical period in China that is often associated with the rule of the Mongolian people."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0b9a9c192485b2833c95724a8a39e749</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SONG DYNASTY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The Song dynasty was a preceding historical period in China, which may have influenced the rebellion of the Yuan dynasty."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0b9a9c192485b2833c95724a8a39e749</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MOON FESTIVAL&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"EVENT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The Moon Festival is a significant cultural event in China, often celebrated with special moon cakes."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0b9a9c192485b2833c95724a8a39e749</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;LIBERAL EDUCATION&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Liberal education refers to a style of education that emphasizes the arts, humanities, and social sciences."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0b9a9c192485b2833c95724a8a39e749</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CONGRESS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Congress is an organization that may have required the report on education reform to clarify its intentions."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0b9a9c192485b2833c95724a8a39e749</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MAINTAIN PEOPLE'S INTEREST&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Maintaining people's interest is a goal often associated with liberal education."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0b9a9c192485b2833c95724a8a39e749</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;DEFINE THE GOVERNMENT'S ROLE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Defining the government's role in education is another goal of liberal education."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0b9a9c192485b2833c95724a8a39e749</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;KEEP A LEADING POSITION&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Keeping a leading position in liberal education is a goal often pursued by institutions like the AAAS."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0b9a9c192485b2833c95724a8a39e749</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;GRANDMOTHER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Grandmother is the author's grandmother, who celebrates her first Christmas without her husband."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-e19ac0ea9ce7df7b442c840ae7a6b627</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CHRISTMAS TREE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ARTIFACT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The Christmas tree is a central decoration during the holiday season."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-e19ac0ea9ce7df7b442c840ae7a6b627</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;STAR&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ARTIFACT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The star is a specific decoration on the Christmas tree, Grandmother's favorite."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-e19ac0ea9ce7df7b442c840ae7a6b627</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CONSUMERS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Consumers are individuals or groups who purchase goods and services."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-2357a4ceb9fc249315f0e66d226ad030</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;RISING GAS COSTS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"EVENT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Rising gas costs are a factor influencing consumer decisions."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-2357a4ceb9fc249315f0e66d226ad030</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PICASSO&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Picasso is described as a painter who struggled to find his own style of painting, indicating a lack of a particular painting style."&lt;SEP&gt;"Picasso was a great Spanish painter known for his unique style and willingness to experiment.")</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5f6b1727ec12c0ea57ccb990781c29f8&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-e3ccdab8a04a9763cd3375eea2c22ba6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ALFRED AND ANTHONY MELILLO&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Alfred and Anthony Melillo are twin brothers from East Haven who made history in 2002.")</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-e3ccdab8a04a9763cd3375eea2c22ba6</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;OASIS OF THE SEAS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"SHIP"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Oasis of the Seas is a cruise ship mentioned in the text, providing guests with experiences."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5f6b1727ec12c0ea57ccb990781c29f8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;LENA LONG&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Lena Long is mentioned as the daughter of Mr. and Mrs. Long, living with them and working in an office."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5f6b1727ec12c0ea57ccb990781c29f8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MR. AND MRS. LONG&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Mr. and Mrs. Long is the father and mother of Lena Long."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5f6b1727ec12c0ea57ccb990781c29f8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;WATTS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Watts is described as a young man who met Lena Long and became friends with her parents."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5f6b1727ec12c0ea57ccb990781c29f8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;DIRECT ECONOMIC LOSSES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Direct economic losses refer to the monetary value lost due to a disaster or event."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5f6b1727ec12c0ea57ccb990781c29f8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;AGRICULTURE, FORESTRY, ANIMAL HUSBANDRY AND FISHERY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"These are sectors that are affected by natural disasters like typhoons."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5f6b1727ec12c0ea57ccb990781c29f8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;INDUSTRIAL AND TRANSPORT SECTOR&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"This sector is also affected by natural disasters."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5f6b1727ec12c0ea57ccb990781c29f8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;WATER CONSERVANCY INFRASTRUCTURE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"This infrastructure is crucial for disaster management and is often damaged by natural disasters."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5f6b1727ec12c0ea57ccb990781c29f8</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;WILD NETWORK&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Wild Network is a collaboration of nearly 400 organizations involved in a campaign to encourage children to spend 30 minutes outdoors each day."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-9568c857ca048a0d94a30cbbb5351272</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;BBC TV SERIES WHY DONT YOU&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The BBC is an organization that aired a TV series in the 1980s encouraging children to spend less time watching TV and more time doing less boring activities."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-9568c857ca048a0d94a30cbbb5351272</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SHERIKH BASHIR M. NUR MOHBASHIIR@GMAIL.COM&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Sherikh Bashir M. Nur Mohbashiir is a contact listed for hiring at IECC, identified by his email address."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-3a4078f1354efff8eb4524a0002b9458</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MRSBASHIIR@GMAIL.COM&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Mrs. Bashir M. Nur Mohbashiir is another contact listed for hiring at IECC, identified by her email address."&lt;SEP&gt;"Mrs. Bashir M. Nur Mohbashiir is another potential candidate for hiring at IECC, identified by her email address."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-3a4078f1354efff8eb4524a0002b9458</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SHERIKH BASHIR M. NUR MOHBASHIIR&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Sherikh Bashir M. Nur Mohbashiir is a potential candidate for hiring at IECC, identified by his email address."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-3a4078f1354efff8eb4524a0002b9458</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PLANTS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"organisms"</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-a7f94c09754ee51df1385a014ae84929</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SEEKING THE SKY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"EVENT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The phrase 'Seeking the Sky' suggests an activity or movement to explore or appreciate the night sky."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-a7f94c09754ee51df1385a014ae84929</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;STARS IN THE SKY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"EVENT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"'Stars in the Sky' could refer to an event, a gathering, or a celebration focused on the observation of stars."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-a7f94c09754ee51df1385a014ae84929</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CITY POLLUTION&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"City pollution refers to the contamination of the urban environment by air, water, and soil pollutants resulting from human activities."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-a7f94c09754ee51df1385a014ae84929</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SANTA&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Santa is the main character in the text, representing the figure of Christmas, known for his reindeer pulling his sleigh."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-6bcd27d566f2cbb8eadc20c2d186ddf3</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;KILLER BEES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANISM"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Killer bees are the main subject of the text, a species of bees that have become a significant ecological and agricultural concern."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-6bcd27d566f2cbb8eadc20c2d186ddf3</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;THE COMPOUND&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The compound is a place of refuge and sanctuary within a bustling world."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-99c826d6be60b5d82daed829657abc3b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ANCIENT OAK TREE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The ancient oak tree stands in the center of the compound, symbolizing resilience and nature's endurance."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-99c826d6be60b5d82daed829657abc3b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CITY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The city is distant and hums quietly in the background, contrasting with the tranquility of the compound."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-99c826d6be60b5d82daed829657abc3b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;INHABITANTS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The inhabitants of the compound are a group of people who share a sense of camaraderie and purpose."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-99c826d6be60b5d82daed829657abc3b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;RESILIENCE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Resilience is a quality of nature and people that endures despite difficulties."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-99c826d6be60b5d82daed829657abc3b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;NATURE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Nature refers to the natural world and its elements."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-99c826d6be60b5d82daed829657abc3b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CHAOS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Chaos is a state of disorder or lack of order."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-99c826d6be60b5d82daed829657abc3b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PEACE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Peace is the state of being free from conflict or unrest."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-99c826d6be60b5d82daed829657abc3b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MOM&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Mom is the one writing the note, indicating the sender is a parent or guardian."&lt;SEP&gt;"Mom is the one writing the note, indicating the sender is a parent or guardian.")&lt;SEP&gt;"Mom is the subject of the narrative, experiencing dementia and expressing concern for her daughter's well-being."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-c8180a672b18d533ab8254b5164b63fc&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-7f97af696c486ef93985da016ed79441</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ALICE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Alice is the girlfriend of the young man Ned Currie, who is dating her when she is a teenager."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-7f97af696c486ef93985da016ed79441</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;NED CURRIE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Ned Currie is the boyfriend of Alice, who is engaged in a relationship with him."&lt;SEP&gt;"Ned Currie is the young man Alice dates, employed at a newspaper and involved in a relationship with her."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-7f97af696c486ef93985da016ed79441</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CHEST FREEZER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"TECHNOLOGY"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Chest freezers are a type of technology that defrost manually, requiring owners to defrost them periodically."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-010faeff10403d34d4f0f7cfa21d9823</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;FROSTLESS FREEZER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"TECHNOLOGY"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Frostless freezers are a type of technology that automatically defrost at present intervals and remove the water."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-010faeff10403d34d4f0f7cfa21d9823</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;TEACHER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Teacher is the profession of a person who prepares and gives instructions to students. Karl's mother is a teacher, trying to talk to her son after his father's death."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-de1aaaa9c767c6c5a40f68baac15512b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ACTOR&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Actor is a person who performs in front of an audience. Karl's mother is an actor, preparing to deliver a speech to her son."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-de1aaaa9c767c6c5a40f68baac15512b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SPEECHMAKER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"A speechmaker is a person who delivers a speech. Karl's mother is a speechmaker, preparing to deliver a speech to her son about his withdrawal after his father's death.")</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-de1aaaa9c767c6c5a40f68baac15512b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;TEACHERS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Teachers are a part of the organization responsible for teaching students."&lt;SEP&gt;"Teachers are the individuals conducting the activity."&lt;SEP&gt;"Teachers are the individuals who may benefit from the activity."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-ad59e76403164aca2ff18000b5e9082d&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-01c65839e016c68dfe2799c20abd707a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ACTORS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Actors are also part of the organization, possibly involved in performances or public speaking."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-01c65839e016c68dfe2799c20abd707a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SPEECHMAKERS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Speechmakers are part of the organization responsible for delivering speeches or messages."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-01c65839e016c68dfe2799c20abd707a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SPOKESMEN&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Spokesmen are part of the organization tasked with representing the organization and conveying its message."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-01c65839e016c68dfe2799c20abd707a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SCHOOL&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"School is the institution where parents share bedtime stories with their children."&lt;SEP&gt;"School is the institution where the activity is taking place."&lt;SEP&gt;"School is the location Andy is going to."&lt;SEP&gt;"The dormitory is associated with the school the student attends, providing a living space for students."&lt;SEP&gt;"The school is the location where Karl is a student."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-ad59e76403164aca2ff18000b5e9082d&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-fce39e4cb7bbfd17f745b6b0a2c17ce3&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-3570d101af27b4cbcee151e3b5d76edc&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-01c65839e016c68dfe2799c20abd707a</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MRS. GATES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Mrs. Gates is the mother of Bruce, who goes to answer the phone."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5e106c3607ab331e17494bc97f475886</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;BRUCE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Bruce is the son of Mrs. Gates and goes to buy bananas."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5e106c3607ab331e17494bc97f475886</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;RACHEL&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Rachel has a daughter named Melissa."&lt;SEP&gt;"Rachel is the daughter of Tom, with whom Tom has had a fight before Melissa was born."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5e106c3607ab331e17494bc97f475886</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MARGE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Marge is Tom's wife, who has died many years before, leaving Tom to live alone."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5e106c3607ab331e17494bc97f475886</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;GARDEN&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Tom lives in a garden where he plants various vegetables and flowers."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5e106c3607ab331e17494bc97f475886</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PUMPKINS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PLANT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Tom likes to plant pumpkins in his garden."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5e106c3607ab331e17494bc97f475886</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PEPPERS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PLANT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Tom likes to plant peppers in his garden."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5e106c3607ab331e17494bc97f475886</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;TOMATOES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PLANT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Tom likes to plant tomatoes in his garden."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5e106c3607ab331e17494bc97f475886</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ZUCCHINI&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PLANT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Tom likes to plant zucchini in his garden."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5e106c3607ab331e17494bc97f475886</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SPINACH&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PLANT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Tom likes to plant spinach in his garden."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5e106c3607ab331e17494bc97f475886</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MODERN WORLD&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Many grown persons have a hard time keeping up with changes in the modern world."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5e106c3607ab331e17494bc97f475886</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SCHOOL STUDENTS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The group of individuals who are asked to buy homework answers through the Internet."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-1abde765b394e15a8df814033fa4e333</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SCHOOL TEACHERS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The teachers who might be providing the homework for the students."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-1abde765b394e15a8df814033fa4e333</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SOCRATES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Socrates is the individual being addressed by the text, known for his teachings and philosophical dialogues."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-7ff83674bec03ab76974d7d7b9b12839</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;YOUNG MAN&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"A passerby who stops to help the little boy, offering to escort him to the king."&lt;SEP&gt;"The young man is the one who wants to buy a new pair of shoes, expressing his desire to relive the joy of receiving new shoes as a child."&lt;SEP&gt;"The young man is the one with whom Socrates engages in conversation, likely someone seeking guidance or advice."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-03c253a2c0b46812f0bc9404a9dfe1cc&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-e8261323f963f0c997bd35634e9eb14b&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-7ff83674bec03ab76974d7d7b9b12839</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;RIVER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The river is the setting for the meeting between Socrates and the young man."&lt;SEP&gt;"The rivers affected by the ferries are located in Bangladesh."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-f0a2b5578c630dd4c0cf72cfe3dc5a47&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-7ff83674bec03ab76974d7d7b9b12839</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;LONDON&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Jack London is a renowned American writer known for his struggles with financial difficulties while writing his books."&lt;SEP&gt;"Jack London promised to write a story for a New York magazine, indicating a professional commitment."&lt;SEP&gt;"London is a city known for its restaurants and diverse population."&lt;SEP&gt;"London is mentioned as a cycling city after bombings."&lt;SEP&gt;"London is the capital city of the United Kingdom and is known for its rich history and culture."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-a6698d96144a3329383053b88a9a352c&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-3ee3a64e9048bb17e5224abaa8512514&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-3447d8d5f9b76de39da0c174d8d45059&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-7ff83674bec03ab76974d7d7b9b12839</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;RESTAURANTS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Restaurants are places where people go to eat, often indicating a high concentration of people and diverse cultures."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-7ff83674bec03ab76974d7d7b9b12839</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ENGLISH PEOPLE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"English people are residents of England and are likely frequent customers of the restaurants mentioned."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-7ff83674bec03ab76974d7d7b9b12839</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CHEAP&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ATTRIBUTE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Cheapness is an attribute of restaurants, suggesting affordability for the customers."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-7ff83674bec03ab76974d7d7b9b12839</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;FOOD&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ATTRIBUTE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Food is an attribute of restaurants, indicating what they serve."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-7ff83674bec03ab76974d7d7b9b12839</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;HAPPY FARMS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"GAME"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Happy Farms is a game that some people play online, indicating its popularity and virtual nature."&lt;SEP&gt;"Happy Farms is the game being referred to, where players engage in virtual farming activities."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-7ff83674bec03ab76974d7d7b9b12839</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;GARDENS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"GAME"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Gardens are a part of the game Happy Farms, suggesting that players might interact with virtual gardens."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-7ff83674bec03ab76974d7d7b9b12839</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CLERK&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"A clerk was fired because she was playing Happy Farms at work, indicating a negative consequence of the game."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-7ff83674bec03ab76974d7d7b9b12839</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;WORK&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Playing Happy Farms at work is a location where the game is being played, possibly at a workplace."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-7ff83674bec03ab76974d7d7b9b12839</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;NARCISSISM&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ATTRIBUTE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Narcissism is an attribute of people who can't see themselves, suggesting a lack of self-awareness."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-7ff83674bec03ab76974d7d7b9b12839</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;BLIND&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The blind individual is the subject of the text, who experiences misconceptions about their abilities."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-7ff83674bec03ab76974d7d7b9b12839</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;HARVARD COLLEGE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Harvard College is an institution known for its strong academic programs, including the Law School."&gt;</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-040b98e8788d89803dfa2cd4b7770f7b</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ZEO&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Zeo is an organization that produces a sleep tracking device."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0457b4fc4516080b570290fa7ef7e925</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;IM NOT A PLASTIC BAG&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PRODUCT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The product is a fashionable, green cotton bag designed to encourage reusable bags over plastic ones."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0457b4fc4516080b570290fa7ef7e925</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PRESIDENT OBAMA&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"President Obama is a person who is very busy and has time to visit schools."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0457b4fc4516080b570290fa7ef7e925</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;DALLAS CHILDREN'S THEATER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Dallas Children's Theater is an organization that offers acting classes."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0457b4fc4516080b570290fa7ef7e925</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PRE-K&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Pre-K is an organization that provides educational programs for young children."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0457b4fc4516080b570290fa7ef7e925</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;NANCY SCHAEFFER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Nancy Schaeffer is a person who is involved in the enrollment process for the acting classes."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0457b4fc4516080b570290fa7ef7e925</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;214-978-0110&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONTACT_METHOD"</data>
      <data key="d1">"214-978-0110 is a phone number where people can contact Nancy Schaeffer."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0457b4fc4516080b570290fa7ef7e925</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;NANCY@DCT.ORG&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"EMAIL"</data>
      <data key="d1">"nancy@dct.org is an email address associated with Nancy Schaeffer."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0457b4fc4516080b570290fa7ef7e925</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;2008&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"NUMERIC_VALUE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"2008 is a year that is mentioned in the ad for the acting classes."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0457b4fc4516080b570290fa7ef7e925</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ACTING CLASSES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"EVENT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Acting Classes is an event that takes place over four weeks."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0457b4fc4516080b570290fa7ef7e925</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;FULL $80 PAYMENT PER STUDENT&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"NUMERIC_VALUE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Full $80 payment per student indicates the cost of enrollment."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0457b4fc4516080b570290fa7ef7e925</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PRE-K (PRE-KINDERGARTEN)&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Pre-K (Pre-Kindergarten) is an organization that provides educational programs for young children."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0457b4fc4516080b570290fa7ef7e925</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ACT IT UP (K-1 &amp;&amp; 2ND-3)&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Act It Up (K-1 &amp;&amp; 2nd-3) is an organization that provides acting classes."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0457b4fc4516080b570290fa7ef7e925</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;AUDITIONS AND MONOLOGUES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"EVENT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Auditions and Monologues is an event that takes place for students grades 7+."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-0457b4fc4516080b570290fa7ef7e925</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;DOORBELL&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The doorbell is the location where the electromagnet is installed, indicating its function in receiving signals."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-dc74783c93ca87af88bd9b273a62b5c0</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ELECTROMAGNET&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"TECHNOLOGY"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Electromagnet is the technology used in the doorbell to generate a sound when activated."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-dc74783c93ca87af88bd9b273a62b5c0</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MARIGOLD&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PLANT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Marigold is the plant species being discussed, which can be cultivated for its flowers."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-dc74783c93ca87af88bd9b273a62b5c0</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;COLLEGE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The college is the organization offering the reward for the pure white marigold."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-dc74783c93ca87af88bd9b273a62b5c0</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;EXPERTS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Experts are mentioned in the text, but they are not the main subject of the passage."&lt;SEP&gt;"Experts are the individuals from the college who doubted the old woman's claim."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-a23a47217d8f71ac1ac9a737cb0f25ed&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-dc74783c93ca87af88bd9b273a62b5c0</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;OLD WOMAN&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The old woman is the individual who received the seeds and grew the marigold over 20 years."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-dc74783c93ca87af88bd9b273a62b5c0</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;HUSBAND&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The husband of the old woman is mentioned as someone who passed away."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-dc74783c93ca87af88bd9b273a62b5c0</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CHILDREN&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Children are described in the text as enjoying housework and not thinking life was boring, which contrasts with the parents' negative view."&lt;SEP&gt;"Children are the future generation, the ones who will inherit and develop the technology."&lt;SEP&gt;"Children are the individuals involved in the activity."&lt;SEP&gt;"Children are the individuals who may benefit from the activity."&lt;SEP&gt;"The children of the old woman are mentioned as being absent when she made her decision."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-04e8e6898cff0ca66fb0ec3913c5a7fb&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-71161dd5267a74aafb42bd1b5ec152bc&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-ad59e76403164aca2ff18000b5e9082d&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-dc74783c93ca87af88bd9b273a62b5c0</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;GENETICS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"FIELD"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Genetics is the field of study that experts might not have been successful in growing the white marigold."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-dc74783c93ca87af88bd9b273a62b5c0</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;BEN'S PARENTS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Ben's parents are his father, who is a doctor, and his mother, who is a teacher."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-79c6ed71ba0d62a4f0967263e1f9832e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CLIFF HOUSE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Cliff House is a location mentioned in the text, presumably where the events described occur."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-79c6ed71ba0d62a4f0967263e1f9832e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;NORTH POLE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"North Pole is a location referenced in the text, specifically the top of the world near the North Pole."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-79c6ed71ba0d62a4f0967263e1f9832e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;NEW YORK STATE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"LOCATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"New York State is a location where the bear would likely survive the winter."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-79c6ed71ba0d62a4f0967263e1f9832e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;PRIMITIVE LIFE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"CONCEPT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"primitive life refers to a time before humans developed more complex societies and technologies."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-79c6ed71ba0d62a4f0967263e1f9832e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ANCIENT TIMES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"TIME"</data>
      <data key="d1">"ancient times refers to periods in the past before the current era."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-79c6ed71ba0d62a4f0967263e1f9832e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;GREEKS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The Greeks are a historical civilization known for their contributions to philosophy, art, and architecture."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-79c6ed71ba0d62a4f0967263e1f9832e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ARABS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The Arabs are a group of people who have a rich history in the fields of science, culture, and diplomacy."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-79c6ed71ba0d62a4f0967263e1f9832e</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CALIFORNIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The California Institute of Technology is an educational institution known for its contributions to science and technology."&lt;SEP&gt;"The California Institute of Technology is an institution known for hosting scientific conferences and discussions on biotechnology."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-79c6ed71ba0d62a4f0967263e1f9832e&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-ff373fddf934c2987392de02390348d2</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;DAVID BALTIMORE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"David Baltimore is a scientist known for his work in genetics and molecular biology."&lt;SEP&gt;"David Baltimore is a scientist who participated in the Asilomar conference and opened a meeting discussing human gene editing."&lt;SEP&gt;"David Baltimore is mentioned as a participant in the Asilomar conference and discusses gene editing in Washington."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-79c6ed71ba0d62a4f0967263e1f9832e&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-ff373fddf934c2987392de02390348d2&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-611fb27ef3c15c1adaf70de79e3055a5</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ASILOMAR CONFERENCE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"EVENT"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The Asilomar conference brought scientists together to discuss the use of recombinant DNA technology."&lt;SEP&gt;"The Asilomar conference brought together scientists to discuss the safe use of recombinant DNA technology."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-ff373fddf934c2987392de02390348d2&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-611fb27ef3c15c1adaf70de79e3055a5</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;NATIONAL SCIENTIFIC ACADEMIES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The meeting was held by national scientific academies, indicating a group of scholars."&lt;SEP&gt;"The national scientific academies of America, Britain, and China organized the Human Gene Editing meeting."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-ff373fddf934c2987392de02390348d2&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-611fb27ef3c15c1adaf70de79e3055a5</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;RECOMBINANT DNA TECHNOLOGY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"TECHNOLOGY"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Recombinant DNA technology is a field of scientific research that involves the combination of DNA from different sources."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-ff373fddf934c2987392de02390348d2</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CRISPR-CAS9&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"TECHNOLOGY"</data>
      <data key="d1">"CRISPR-Cas9 is a gene-editing tool that uses RNA and an enzyme to target and modify DNA."&lt;SEP&gt;"CRISPR-Cas9 is a technology used in genetics research."&lt;SEP&gt;"CRISPR-Cas9 is a tool that involves RNA and an enzyme."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-ff373fddf934c2987392de02390348d2&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-611fb27ef3c15c1adaf70de79e3055a5&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-5da536f0ee254ed1c2b5727daf4629e5</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;IMMUNE SYSTEM&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANISM"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The immune system is a complex biological system that defends the body against harmful pathogens."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-ff373fddf934c2987392de02390348d2</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;T-CELLS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANISM"</data>
      <data key="d1">"T-cells are a type of white blood cell that plays a crucial role in the immune system."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-ff373fddf934c2987392de02390348d2</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;LEBER CONGENITAL AMAUROSIS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"DISEASE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Leber congenital amaurosis is a rare genetic condition that causes vision loss."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-ff373fddf934c2987392de02390348d2</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;AMERICAN ASSOCIATION FOR THE ADVANCEMENT OF SCIENCE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"An organization involved in scientific meetings and research."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-6afb8625dcde8fbcbc8cb5bd6c752889</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SCIENTISTS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Scientists conducting research and presenting findings."&lt;SEP&gt;"The individuals who advised the farmers to mix pesticides with a sugary juice."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-1082a3b5cfb204090f0be93ef1fd174e&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-6afb8625dcde8fbcbc8cb5bd6c752889</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CARBON DIOXIDE&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"SUBSTANCE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Carbon dioxide is a greenhouse gas mentioned in relation to food production and environmental impact."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-6afb8625dcde8fbcbc8cb5bd6c752889</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MEAT&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"SUBSTANCE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Meat is a food product that contributes to greenhouse gas emissions."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-6afb8625dcde8fbcbc8cb5bd6c752889</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;COW&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ANIMAL"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Cows are raised on farmland and contribute to methane production, a potent greenhouse gas."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-6afb8625dcde8fbcbc8cb5bd6c752889</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;HAMBURGER&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"SUBSTANCE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Hamburger is a concept mentioned in the passage, possibly referring to a food item."&lt;SEP&gt;"Hamburgers are a food product that requires energy and contributes to greenhouse gas emissions."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-5b555aba0363adca7fdcb5beb10a70de&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-6afb8625dcde8fbcbc8cb5bd6c752889</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;POTATO&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"SUBSTANCE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Potatoes require less carbon dioxide to produce than meat and are considered a better environmental choice."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-6afb8625dcde8fbcbc8cb5bd6c752889</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ANDY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Andy is a person who goes to school and daydreams about fishing."&lt;SEP&gt;"Andy is the main character experiencing a panic attack while riding to school."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-fce39e4cb7bbfd17f745b6b0a2c17ce3&lt;SEP&gt;chunk-6afb8625dcde8fbcbc8cb5bd6c752889</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;JONAS BROTHERS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"ORGANIZATION"</data>
      <data key="d1">"The Jonas Brothers is a popular boy band featured in Camp Rock."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-fce39e4cb7bbfd17f745b6b0a2c17ce3</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;DEMI LOVATO&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Demi Lovato is a teenage girl with an extraordinary voice in Camp Rock."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-fce39e4cb7bbfd17f745b6b0a2c17ce3</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;MITCHIE TORRES&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Mitchie Torres is a character in Camp Rock who helps her mom at the expensive music camp."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-fce39e4cb7bbfd17f745b6b0a2c17ce3</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;SHANE GRAY&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Shane Gray is a member of Connect Three and is sent to a music camp to help clean up his act."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-fce39e4cb7bbfd17f745b6b0a2c17ce3</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;CAMP ROCK&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"MOVIE"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Camp Rock is the movie that features the Jonas Brothers and attracts a large audience."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-fce39e4cb7bbfd17f745b6b0a2c17ce3</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;LEAH KARRELS&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Leah Karrels is a teenage girl who sings the movie's theme and is eager to watch the movie."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-fce39e4cb7bbfd17f745b6b0a2c17ce3</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ALEXANDER HAMILTON&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
      <data key="d1">"Alexander Hamilton is a historical figure associated with the founding of the United States, likely referenced in the context of the passage about a convenient location near Washington, D.C."</data>
      <data key="d2">chunk-74d233aaadef3b485a495bffcf8d27fd</data>
    </node>
    <node id="&quot;ALEX&quot;">
      <data key="d0">"PERSON"</data>
